htmart.com 2006-11-06

# Home Theater Mart :: Privacy Policy

**HT MART Privacy Policy**

Our Commitment to Privacy:  
HT MART is sensitive to Internet privacy issues and respects our customer's privacy! We value our relationship with you and we hold your personal information in the strictest confidence. 

This policy explains how HT MART treats information that we may gather about you while you visit the HT MART web site. The purpose of this policy is to inform the visitors to the HT MART web site about the different kinds of information we may collect and whether we disclose it to anyone. Please note that this policy applies only to our web site and not to any third-party web sites to which we may link. HT MART cannot be responsible for the content or the privacy policies employed by any other sites. 

In general, you can visit the HT MART web site as an anonymous visitor without revealing any information about yourself. Our site servers automatically track certain usage information, but this information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. 

The Type of Information We Collect:  
There are times when we do need to gather personal information from our site customers, such as when you register to use our site or when you order merchandise from our web site. In those cases we may need to collect certain contact and billing information such as your name, billing address, email address, phone number, and credit card number. 

In addition, on some pages you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift certificate, and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to supply the recipient's name, physical and/or email address, and phone number. The recipient information you provide will only be used to send the gift certificate. 

How We Use the Information:  
HT MART may use this personal contact information to fulfill your product purchases and service requests; provide you with order details; support services and to customize/personalize your shopping experience. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the order. For example, this information may be disclosed to our staff and to third-parties involved in your online transaction including but not limited to order fulfillment, billing and shipping companies. 

We use return email addresses to reply to the email inquires we receive. 

Our site servers automatically track certain usage information such as the number of visitors, frequency of visitors, time of visits, pages visited and referring web sites, so as to improve our site through statistical analysis. 

What are cookies, and how are they used?  
Cookies are small text files that serve as an identifier and are stored on your computer when you visit pages that record your preferences. HT MART uses cookies to create a more personalized shopping experience, such as to remember what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to our store. Cookies placed on your computer by HT MART will not harm your computer and they do not contain any personal or private information. You must allow your web browser to accept cookies to shop at HT MART. 

How can I Decide what kinds of Marketing Communications I will Receive?  
HT MART may send you marketing communications that contain offers, promotions, contests and other content we think you might find of interest. You always have the option to opt-in or opt-out of receiving future marketing communications from HT MART. To opt-in or opt-out, please follow the directions on the bottom of a marketing email. 

Our Commitment to Security:  
We use industry-standard 128-bit encrypted SSL (Secure Socket Layer) to protect your information. HT MART follows reasonable technical and management practices to provide for the integrity, safety, security and confidentiality of transactions and data stored on our servers. As an additional layer of customer security, we do not store customer's credit card numbers on the HT MART server. You can confirm you are on a secure checkout page by observing https:// in your web browser's URL address bar. The "s" after http:// stands for "secure". You can also verify that the browser's padlock icon should be locked or key icon should be unbroken along the bottom of your browser's window, while you are on checkout pages dealing with credit card information. 

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:  
Protecting the privacy of young children is important to HT MART. HT MART is a general audience site and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. Our site is intended to be used by adult visitors who are looking for information, services, or to purchase merchandise. By registering with HT MART and purchasing products from HT MART, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 18, you must ask your parent or legal guardian to facilitate the order. 

How to Access and/or Modify Your Information:  
You can access all of your personally identifiable user information that we collect by logging into your user account. Click Here to [Login to your User Account ](http://www.htmart.com/help.php?section=myaccount)and enter your username and password. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

Choosing a login Password at HT MART:  
For increased security, please select a password that is 5-10 characters in length and contains a combination of letters and numbers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account information. You have the option to make a purchase from our web site without creating a user account and password. However, each time you return to our site to make a purchase, you will have to re-enter your personal information. 

Disclosure to Privacy Policy Exceptions:  
We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights. We may disclose your information if it relates to threatened or harmful conduct or HT MART has good faith reason to believe that such action is necessary to conform to the requirements of law, comply with government orders, court orders or other legal process. HT MART may disclose your information to protect and defend our property and/or rights, the users of this web site or the public at large. This includes exchanging information with third-party companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk protection. If HT MART should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may sell and/or share the information you provide us to a third-party or with the company we merge with. 

How to Contact Us:  
Should you have other questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please call us at 404-353-3412 or [Contact Us](http://www.htmart.com/help.php?section=contactus&mode=update) here. 

Your Consent to this Privacy Policy:  
By using the HT MART web site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. It is your responsibility to review our privacy policy and remain informed about any changes to it. 

This site and its contents, unless specifically noted, are copyright HT MART © 2005 - 2020\. Unauthorized use of site content is prohibited. All rights reserved. 

Please visit the HT MART [Help Zone](http://www.htmart.com/help.php) with any other questions you may have regarding our policies. 

HT MART Privacy Policy last updated on November 09, 2005 

\--- Return to Top of Page ---
